[MUSIC PLAYING]
ROB DODSON: 大家好
ROB DODSON: Hey there, polycasters!
我是Rob  今天节目的主持人
Rob here, interrupting your regularly scheduled program
为你带来
to bring you this.
Chrome开发者大会的情况
It's the Chrome Developers Summit,
大会正在进行
and it's going on right now, unless you're
除非你看的是视频回顾
watching this in the future.
但不管这么说  所有内容
But either way, all of the content
都可以在Chrome Developers这个YouTube频道上找到
is available up on the Chrome Developers YouTube channel.
我们请到了Paul Lewis和Paul Irish
We've got talks from Paul Lewis and Paul Irish
讲解构建高性能的网页应用
on building performant web apps, Alice Boxhall
Alice Boxhall讲解无障碍功能
talks about accessibility, and Taylor Savage
Taylor Savage讲解如何用Polymer构建先进的网页应用
and yours truly about building progressive web apps using Polymer.
一定要去看哦
So definitely go check that out, and I'll
下周的Polycast我会带来全新的一集
catch you back here next week for a brand-new episode of Polycast.
[MUSIC PLAYING]